

Nguyen Tri Hoang

Date of birth: February 22, 1997

Gender: Male

Phone: 0337983068

Email: hoangnt.working@gmail.com

Address: Hanoi, Vietnam

OBJECTIVE

-Short-term goal:

+ Working at the company as a back-end, devops to further improve their professional knowledge and gain more work experience - contribute to the growth of the company they are participating in.

+ Learn technologies such as AI, machine learning, big data ...

-Long-term goals:

+ Become Solution Architect as well as an important part of your company.

EDUCATION

Sep 2015 - Dec 2019

Post and Telecommunications Institute of Technology

Major: Software Technology

GPA: 3.13/4.0

WORK EXPERIENCE

Jul 2020 - Present

GHTK

Developer

- Develop application g-chats
- Activities : + Design system (architecture back-end, database).
 - + Optimization, scale the system back-end.
 - + Scale system real-time (use kafka connect).
 - + Logging job kafka, system back-end.
 - + Synchronization between systems in ghtk (use CDC).
 - + Cache for system back-end.
 - + Write system notification.
 - + Write endpoint for mobile, web use java.
- Business : System chat shop, buyer, customer care, internal.

Sep 2019 - Jul 2020

Septeni technology

Developer

- Develop application web.
- Activities : Write backend use Scala, frontend use Vue ts, system
- design, custom library, scrum framework.
- Business : Project management, customers, employees, assign tasks to employees,...

Dec 2018 - Feb 2019

Lien Viet Post Bank

Part-time intern

- Block Information Technology (Information System Application Management Department)

SKILLS

- Programming language: Java, Scala, C, C++, js. - Kafka, Kafka connect, Spring, Spring boot, JPA, Hibernat, Security, Servlet, Play, Vue, Microservice Architecture(base). - Mobile: android base. - IDE: Intellij, Eclipse, Spring tool suite, Android studio. - Database: MySQL, Cassandra, Sql Server. - Search: Elasticsearch. - Cache: Redis. - Restfull, git. Soft skills - Hardworking, always actively learning and exploring. - Ability to work in groups and work independently. - Withstand high work pressure.

INTERESTS

- Participate in social activities.
- Enjoy sports activities: football, volleyball,
- Enjoy reading and surfing the web.
- Enjoy traveling and connecting friends....

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Link facebook : https://www.facebook.com/tri.hoang.3382.
- I hope to be joined in the company. Contribute a bit of energy to your company and become a member of your company.